Guide to the Montana State Prison records 1864-1974
Montana Historical Society
- Montana State Prison
  - Prisoner Records
    - Prisoner description sheets: Julius Otonochar, Micheal S. Ott, Angela Otter Bull, Clarence Ouelette, Edward Oulette, Lawrence Oulette, Cyr Ouellett, Blondy B. Overall, Art Overby, Bobbie Joe Overton, Albert Overturf, Ralph Thomas Owen, Raymond T. Owen, Charles Owens, D.H. Owens, Daniel Owens, Herman M. Owens, James Thorpe Owens, Kenneth Owen, Nelson Owens, Raymond Owens, Wade Owens, William V. Owens, Watson M. Oyler, 1923-1960 (Box-folder 66/2)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Merlyn Pace, Martin Pachero, Robert Pachett, Thomas Packhan, Richard Wilson Packineau, Irvin Paddock, M.N. Paddock, Elias Padilia, John Padilia, Joe Padilla, Ray Padilla, Jack Page, Orville Page, John Pahlke, Henry Painter, Samuel Palama, Frank Palffy, Wallace Palm, Bud Palmer, Earl Palmer, Palmer George, George D. Palmer, Hugh Palmer, James E. Palmer, Leo W. Palmer, William Palmer, William Fred Palmer, Lorenzo M. Panalez, John c. Pancake, Egbert Pandolfo, Nicolas Panegura, Caesar Panerio, Ralph Fred Pangburn, Albert Panicco, Tony Panion, Raymond Panko, Sheldon S. Pankow, Pantelides Savas, Nick Papas, Madison J. Pape, Angelo Papillo, George Papparumpus (alias George Papaus), Donet Paquette, Frank Paranteau, Daniel Parce, Donaciano Paredez, Thomas Parenteau, Gust Paris, Fred Pariseau, William Parizeau, 1923-1960 (Box-folder 66/3)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Harry Park, A.L. Parker, Arthur Parker, Daniel Parker, Jack Parker, Jess Parker, Marion O'Neill Parker, Robert Richard Parker, George Parkies, Thomas Parkins, George Parks, Henry Parks, Robert Parks, Jess William Parlow (alias John W. Wilcox), Clifton Parr, Jess Parr, Francisco Sactillo Parra, Martin Parrent, Jim Parris, Cifford Parrish, Joe E. Parrish, Alvin A. Parschall, Harold Parson, G.C. Parsons, Marcelius S. Parsons, Sanford Parsons, Jack Partee, John D. Partlow, Leon Pase, John P. Pask, Edward J. Patalas, Martha Patkovich, Eugene Patneaude, LaRue Patnode, Eddie G. Patrick, Hubert Patrick, Lazell Patrick, Charles Edward Patterson, Ed Patterson (alias John E. Patterson), James Franklyn Patterson, John Patterson, John Patterson, M.L. Patterson, Oscar C. Patterson, Pat Patterson, Robert F. Patterson, William Patterson, 1923-1960 (Box-folder 66/4)
    - Prisoner description sheets: George E. Pattibone, Daniel Lee Pattie, Ralph Patton, Robert G. Patton, Terrance Patton, Terry Patton, Andrew Paul, Ben Paul, Frank Paul, George Paul, John Paul, Rene Paul, Robert Paul, Tony Paul, Warren B. Paul, Roger Wallace Paull, Thomas Paull, Richard Frederick Paulsen, Gurrimo Pavoreal, Melvin Payette, Birdsell Payne, Lee Payne Jr., Pryor J. Payne, Willard Payton, Golden Peacher, Herbert Pearcy, Walter Franklin Pearl, Buster Pearson, Edgar Pearson, Ervin Pearson, Joseph Pearson, Robert E. Pearson, Thomas Pearson, Sylvester J. Pease, Clyde A. Peay, Allen Pecor, Jerry Pecore (alias Jerry Stevens), Ben Pederson, Gordon Lloyd Pederson, Robert Peeler, Leroy Peerboom, Harry Peet, Joe Pelchie, Jack Arthur Pelesky, William H. Pelham, Herman Pelke, Andy Pellitier, Ben E. Peltchie, Ray Peltier, 1923-1960 (Box-folder 66/5)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Bob Pemberton, Earl L. Pemberton, William Pembroke, Epigmino Caudillo Pena, Cruz Penaloza, William Pendercraft, Earl H. Pendry, Robert Penneypacker, John A. Pennington, Robert R. Pennington, Earl Clifford Penstrom, John O. Pentz, Albart Peoples, James Pephyr, Vince Pepion, Ruben Perez, Teranquileon Perez, Harry N. Perham, Francis M. Perkins, Morris J. Perkins, William James Perkins, Willie Perkins, Constance Pernot, Lester Perrin, Orval Perring, Orville Perring, James Perrington, A.V. Perry, Alex Perry, Charles J. Perry, Clarence A. Perry, Lee Howard Perry, Vernon B. Perry, Butler Ralston Perryman, Taylor Perryman, Edward Peschon, 1923-1960 (Box-folder 66/6)
    - Prisoner description sheets: James Petel, Franklin G. Peterkin, Carl Peters, Donald Peters, Earl Peters, Ralph Peters, Ralph Peters, Alfred Peterson, Alvin F. Peterson, Christian Peterson, Curtis Peterson, Donald Peterson, Donald James Peterson, Duane K. Peterson, E.A. Peterson, Frank Peterson, Gerald Peterson, Harold R. Peterson, Harry Peterson, Jack Martin Peterson, John Peterson, John Merrit Peterson, Lionel B. Peterson, Oscar Peterson, Paul Peterson, Raymond Peterson, Raynen W. Peterson, Richard E. Peterson, Robert Lee Peterson, Roy Peterson, William Peterson, Herbert Petet, Mike Petrillo, Robert Frank Petronek, Herman Petros, Donald Gilbert Petrowsky, Jack Petty, Darwin Pfeifer, Raymond B. Pfeifer, Everett Pfieffer, Frank Prfimmer, 1923-1960 (Box-folder 66/7)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Leo Phalen, Leo M. Phalen, Arthur Phares, Francis Phelps, Talbert Phelps, William David Phelps, Wandle P. Philamlee Jr., Walker Philbeck, Jack Philbrick, Visper E. Philips (alias Earl Kennedy), Joe Steven Phillippi, Archie Phillips, Buck Charles Phillips, Carleton Phillips, Charles Phillips, Cleo Phillips, Donald Edward Phillips, Edward Minor Phillips, Eugene Phillips, Eugene W. Phillips, Frank Phillips, Harold Phillips, Jack Phillips, John A. Phillips, Laverne Phillips, Lee Phillips, Louis R. Phillips, Melvin Phillips, Wilbur Phillips, William Harold Phillips, Joe Phipps, Jimmy Piano, Eddie Pichette, Mike Pichette, Narcisse Pichette, Kenneth F. Pickett, Richard Pickett, Clifford Pidcock, 1923-1960 (Box-folder 66/8)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Albert L. Pierce, Chester Pierce, Edward Pierce, Elmer Pierce, F.H. Pierce, George Pierce, John Byron Pierce, Lambert Pierce, Waldo Pierce, Archie Piercy, James Piermont, Joe Pierre, Pattrick Pierre, Jack L. Pierrie, George Pierson, Rayburn Pierson, Arnold Pietila, George Pietsch, Eddy Pilch, John Pilch, Gilbert Pilcher, Ray Pilkington, Harris Pilley, Earl Pillsbury, Robert F. Pilz, Harland Ping, Lee Ping, Wright Hale Pinkham, Fred Pinnow, Frank A. Pinson, Mary Marie Piper, Marvin Otis Pipes, Walter Pipinich, Paul Pippenger, Frank Pirker, John Pirtle, Benjamin F. Pitkannon, Jake Plaggerman, Richard H. Plauck, Laverne F. Pleaugh, Walter Pleshko, George Pleyer, Oscar Plitt, Roy E. Plotnick, Paul Plumage, Leslie Plummer, James T. Plyler, 1923-1960 (Box-folder 66/9)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Jack Pobantz, Billie S. Pockrus, Alex Podeilski, Kyle Podoll, Herman W. Poe, Jim Poe, Ralph Poindexter, Robert D. Pointdexter, Leonard F. Poirier, Albert James Poitra, Clarence Poitra, Melvin Francis Poitra, Oscar L. Poitra, Jack Poletto, John Poletto, Roger Politiski, Robert Pollard, Oren E. Pollert, Clifford Pomarleau, Clifford Pomeroy, Jesus Ponce, Hubert James Ponchaud, Wong Pong, Adam Ponick, Norbert Ponthier, Laurel Pontius, Cecil Edward Poole, Robert M. Poole, Wilson B. Poole, Clarence Poor, Clyde Lee Poor, Cleo Poorman, George Langley Pope, Paul Pope, Arthur Popham, Charles Popham, Dave Popham, Danny Popovich, Maurice A. Popovich, 1923-1960 (Box-folder 66/10)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Thomas Porantau, Carl Albert Porter, Cecil Porter, Christ Porter, Clarence Porter, J.E. Porter, James Porter, Jane Porach, M.H. Porter, Ray Porter, Robert Porter, Charles Posa, H.W. Posey, Lewis Pospisil, Richard L. Pospisil, John L. Poteet, Albert Potter, Earl Potter, Everrett Potter, Harold E. Potter, Harrison Potter, James Potter, John Clyde Potter, Melvin L. Potter, Robert Gale Potter (alias Jack Monroe), Roy Potterson, Edward Jahnoka Pound, Grant Alfred Pound, Harold Powderface, Alva Dexter Powell, Donald R. Powell, Leonard Powell, Lester Powell, Roy Powell, Howard Powelson, Emil Powers, James Powers (alias Tommy Parvin), Joe Powers, W. Powers, Walter Powers, Wiltsie W. Powers, W. Edward Prall, Conrad R. Pratt, Conrad Robert Pratt, Gus Pratt, Keith Pratt, Donald Prause, Toney Prebish, Ben H. Preisz, Stephen Dustin Prescott, Jerry Prest, Allen W. Prestholt, Clarence Preston, Mike Prevo, 1923-1960 (Box-folder 66/11)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Claude Price, Donald E. Price (alias Don McLean), John Price, Kimball Price, Robert Price, Roy W. Price, Richard Pride, William J. Pride, Laura Priest, Louis Primeau, Louis Primeaux, Clyde Primm, Elmer Primm, Jack Pennington Prince, James Prince, Robert Prior, Dan Prise, Frederic H. Pritchard, James Thomas Pritchett, Robert Leslie Pritchett, Tom Pritchett, William H. Pritchett, James Proctor, Ralph Procter, Donald Proetel, Floyd Proffitt, Joe Pronto, Marten Pronto, Clarence E. Proper, 1923-1960 (Box-folder 66/12)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Henry Prue, Clendon Gerald Pruitt, Clendon Gerald Pruitt, Jacob Phillip Pryma, Jayne Pryor, Lewis Pryor, William K. Pryor, Gabriel Przepiura, Carl Pugh, George Pugh, Joe Pulinske, Joe Pullen, Donald W. Pullman, Harry Lee Pulver Jr., Arthur Purdum, George Purkett, Ronnie Purkett, Donald J. Pursley, Virgil Puttoff (alias John Foley), Virgil Harold Puttoff (alias Virgil Carter), Joe Putzel, Paul Gene Pyatt, Elmer Ray Pyle, 1923-1960 (Box-folder 66/13)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Russell Quackenbush, Charles R. Queen, William Patrick Quinlan (alias William Long), Estella Quinn, Ralph Quinn, Benito Quintana, John Quintana, Bert Quick, Charles Quickenden, Arthur Quicksall, Alfred Quilliam, Hum Quock, 1923-1960 (Box-folder 66/14)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Henry Raab, Emil Raatz, Bob Rabe, Ed Rabe, Robert D. Rabe, Fred Rabine, Billy Allen Rabon, Craig Race, Aaron Racine, Abe Racine, Newton Racine, John Racz, George Radcliffe, Charles W. Rader, Otto C Rader, Bill Radovich, Rufus Raffety, Stanley Ragsdale, Don L. Ragsdill, Thomas Raider (alias Thomas Mitchell), Alfred Raine, John Raines, Paul Raines, James Rainey, Wayne Edward Ralph, Juan Ramainez, Florentino Ramierz, Felix Arriaga Ramirez, Higinio Ramirez, Pedro Ramirez, Pete Ramirez, Salvador Ramirez, Manual Ramoris, H.L. Ramey, Lee Ramey, Manuel Ramos, Frank Ramus, Stanley Rand, William Rand, Ervin Randall, James Roger Randall, Hubert Randol, Leo G. Rangel, Roque Rangel, Lee Raper, Claude Rasmussen, James Rasmussen, Theo Rasmussen, Thomas George Rasmussen, George Ratigan, Martha Ratkovich, Nick Ratkovich, Clyde S. Ratliff, Luther Raul, Clifford Harry Raush, George Raven, Harley Paul Ravencroft, Charles Raw, Dyas Rawlings, 1923-1960 (Box-folder 66/15)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Charles Ray, Charles O. Ray, Claude Ray, George Ray, James Ray, Jefferson Ray, Joe Ray, John Ray (alias John Wilson), M.L. Ray, Donna Azure Raya, Thomas Raye, Joe Rayes, Carl Raymond, James Schuyler Raymond, Maurice H. Raymond, Henry Edward Reagan, Chester Reames, Harvey Reams, Alfred Rear, Matt Rebich, Mike F. Rebrovich, Rufus Rector, William Jordan Redboy, Michel Red Crow, Aloecius Red Fox, Ruby Red Fox, James Redhorse, Carl Redimen, John Redman, William Redmon, Keith Redmond, Russell Redmond, Austin A. Redner, Jasper Redrobe, L.J. Redus, J.R. Reece, William F. Reece, Buster Reed, C.P. Reed, Charles Reed, Charles M. Reed, Everal Reed, James Reed, Paul Milton Reed, R.C. Reed, Richard Reed, Robert Reed, Robert L. Reed, Robert Leeroy Reed, Robert M. Reed, Stanley Reed, Vern Reed, William C. Reed, Lee Reene, Ralph W. Rees, Jesse Albert Reetz, Buck Reeves, George Reeves, 1923-1960 (Box-folder 66/16)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Clifford Regan, William James Regan, Micheal Reggo, Leonard Reich, Arthur Leo Reichmand, Claude Reid, Donald Reid, Lenton Reid, Robert Reid, William T. Reid, James Reidy, Reinhold D. Reiger, William Hubert Reihl, Ed Rein, Ruben Reinaga, Lee Reine, Adolph Reinhardt, Ted Reinhardt, J. Wagner Reinhold, J.R. Reisenaurer, Jake Reiss, Carl Reitz, Howard F. Relling, Juan Remainez, Floyd Reman, Floyd Reman, Ed Remington, Rodolfo Rendon, Lee Reney, Frank Renora, Joe H. Renville, Calvin Renz, John Resinger, George Resser, Bennett Reule, Bonifacio Revera, Lawrence Rexroth, Daniel Clifford Rey, Refigio Reyez, Andrew O. Reynolds, Charles Ross Reynolds, Ellsworth E. Reynolds, Eugene R. Reynolds (alias Sam Arnold), Frank Reynolds, George Reynolds, Harold Reynolds, Jack M. Reynolds, John W. Reynolds, Kenneth W. Reynolds, Roger Reynolds, Roscoe C. Reynolds, Filomeno Reynoso, 1923-1960 (Box-folder 67/1)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Eugene Lwwrence Rhoades, George William Rhoades, William A. Rhoades, William Laverne Rhoades, Joe H. Rhoades, Frank W. Rhodes, George W. Rhodes, Julian Ribra, Charles E. Rice, Eugene Rice, John Glen Rice, Rex Rice, T.R. Rice, James Richard, John d. Richards, Leo Richards, Minnie Richards, Royal Lee Richards, Thomas Richards, Wayne E. Richards, Arde Richardson, Charles Allen Richarson, Clyde Norvin Richardson, Douglas Richardson, Ernest Richardson, Floyd Richardson, George Richardson, Horice Richardson, Marshall Richardson, Olaf Richardson, Robertson E. Richardson, Royal S. Richardson, Virgil Richardson, William Richardson, Roy R. Richtmyer, Albert Richard, Arthur C. Rickman, Chester Rickman, Herbert T. Rickman, Eldon C. Ricks, Petro Rico, 1923-1960 (Box-folder 67/2)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Alexander Howard Riddle, Duane M. Riddle, James Martin Riddle, Donald Leo Rider, Aloysius Rides-At-The-Door, Nick Riebald, Dale John Riebe, LeRoy Riedlinger, John Rickena, John Jolmer Riekki, Paul Rigdon, Carl Johan Riggs, Ardel Riley, Charles Riley, Harry Riley, John P. Riley, John Patrick Riely, William Riley, Richard Kenneth Rinehart, William Ringeisen, Fredrick Ludwig Ringel, William Everett Rinkel, Jose Rios, Phillip Rios, Avery Long Risinger, Demarle Enoch Ritchie, J.R. Ritchie, Slater B. Ritchie, Henry Ritter, Jose Rivera, Joseph Rivera, Juan Rivera, Alta May Rivers, Frankie Rivers, Louis J. Rivers, J.M. Roach, Thomas E. Roach, William H. Roadhouse, Connie E. Roark, 1923-1960 (Box-folder 67/3)
    - Prisoner description sheets: David Robbins, George Robbins, Glenn Robbins, Ray Robbins, W. Robert, DeWayne Roberts, Earl D. Roberts, Edna Roberts, F.D. Roberts, George Roberts, Harold Roberts, J.D. Roberts, James Roberts, James Roberts, John Roberts, Lawrence Roberts, Maxwell A. Roberts, Patrick L. Roberts, Roy Roberts, Thomas William Roberts, William Roberts, Bertram H. Robertson, Chester Robertson, Chet Robertson, Harry Robertson, Joseph Albert Robertson, Michael B. Robertson, Milton A. Robertson, Orlando T. Robinson, William Edwin Robertson, Clarence Robideau, Edward Oliver Robideau, Russell A. Robinette, Allen E. Robinson, Charles Robinson, Claude Robinson, David Robinson, Dudley Robinson, Gerald Dean Robinson, Glenn Robinson, Harold P. Robinson, James Robinson, Joe Robinson, Lee Robinson, O.B. Robinson, Ora Robinson, Orlando T. Robinson, Robert Robinson, Robert J. Robinson, 1923-1960 (Box-folder 67/4)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Roy M. Robinson, Sam Robinson, Wendell Paul Robinson, Woodrow Robinson, Kenneth V. Robison, Joe Robledo, Jack Robson, William Henry Rochester, Dewey Henry Rock, William Rockinger, Eric A. Rockstrom, Alfred Roco, Earl Rodd, John Rodel, William E. Rodey (alias Jack Russell), Alvin E. Rodgers, Edward Rodgers, Jack Rodgers, Jack Rodgers, William Rodgers, Juan Rodiguz, Joseph C. Rodish, E.L. Rodman, Chone Rodriguez, Cornelio Rodriguez, Emileano Rodriguez, Francisco C. Rodriguez, Jesus Rodriguez, Theodore Rodriguez, Aurelis Rodriguz, Felixiano Rodriquez, Manuel Rodriques, Holmes Roe, Alma Jane Roebuck, Benny Joe Roehm, Albert Rogers, Carl Rogers, Clifford Rogers, 1923-1960 (Box-folder 67/5)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Clyde Albert Rogers, Ed Rogers, Edward Rogers, Frank Rogers, Frederick Rogers, Gordon B. Rogers, Joe Rogers, Leo Clarence Rogers, Mayes Eugene Rogers, R.L. Rogers, Richard Rogers, Robert Rogers (alias R.J. Ward), Robert M. Rogers, William Rogers, William Rogers (alias Lewis Art), Thomas Rogic, Jose Rogo, Whitey Rohdes, Jack Rohr, Arthur William Rohrer, Jose Rojo, John Rolcke, Vic Rolf, John Joseph Roll, John Joseph Roll, Troy Roller, Edward E. Rollins, Edwin Rollins, Frank Rolph, Ned Roman, Martin Romaz, Eduardo Romero, Freddie Romero, Golden Romero, Juan A. Romero, Sostenes Romero Jr., Harold G. Rominger, Peter Rondas, Dale L. Rongstad, Henrique Ronquillo, Lawrence Ronquillo, Marco Rooriquez, F.J. Root, Willis Root, Belton Roper, Cleve Roper, 1923-1960 (Box-folder 67/6)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Ben Rosa, Rufine Rosales, Jesus Rosas, Steve Rosbarsky, Carl Rose, George Rose, J.A. Rose, James Rose, Lester Rose, Wayne Rose, Russell Rosenberger, Roy Richard Rosenthal, Joseph Rosinger, Albert Ross, Anthony Ross, Cleo Ross, David J. Ross, Frank Ross, Fred H. Ross, G.E. Ross, Herbert Ross, James A. Ross, Jesse Ross, John Alfred Ross, Joseph L. Ross, Charles H. Rossell, Norbert Rossignol, Elmer Rost, Elmer Rost, Charles Retallack, J.S. Roten, Gilbert Roth, Gilbert Roth, Louis J. Roth, Peter Roth, Valery Thomas Roth, W.H. Rothermel, Norman Rotvold, Leonard Dominic Roufs, Uhlam Roulette, Andrew Roundman, Herman Rounds, Willis Rounds, Joe Roush, William Rousseau, William Rousseau, 1923-1960 (Box-folder 67/7)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Aubrey Rowe, Clarence Dale Rowe, Fred Rowe, Fred Ellis Rowe, George Rowe, Royle C. Rowe, Thomas Rowe, Wilbur Rowe, Harry Rowell, David E. Rowland, Donald Francis Rowland, Judd F. Rowland, Ray Rowland, Theodore Rowland, Charles Rowlins, Thomas Joseph Roy Jr., Jose Arthur Roybal, Nick Roybal, Tony Rozinka, Ed Ruane, Antonio Rubalcava, Darrel A. Rubens, Mike Rubich Jr., Harold Ruby, Jack Ruby, Frank Rucker, Helmar Rud, J.H. Rudd, John Rude, Eli Rudman Jr., Charles Curtis Rudolph, Clarence L. Ruedin, Alex Ruff, Lawrence A. Ruff, Albert W. Rugg, Jose Ruiz, Rudolph O. Ruiz, Harold Ruland, Pete Rule, Carl H. Rumbaugh, Dale Rumbaugh, Warren Rumer, Claude Rumley, Thomas Rummell, Roy Cecil Rumsey, 1923-1960 (Box-folder 67/8)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Fred Runkel, Roy Runnells, Stanley Runner, Albert Running, Robert Gene Runyon, Bill Rupe, Francis Rupe, Charles Rush, John Edward Rushlow, Arthur Rusk, Buster Rusk, Charles E. Rusk, Harry Maynard Rusk, Hugh Rush, Kenneth Russ, Arthur Russell (alias Ted Baker), Charles Russell, Everett Russell, Frank Russell, Harry Russell, Jack A. Russell, Jack Russell, James T. Russell, Jerry Russell, John Wilbur Russell, Johnny Russell, Ronald Russell, Stanley Russell, William Theodore Russell Jr., Mike Russette, Thomas Rutherford, Donald W. Rutledge, Edward Ryan, Gerald R. Ryan, Henry Ryan (aliases Tex Hart; Archie Thompson; Archie Thomas), James Ryan, James Michael Ryan, Lee Ryan, LeRoy Ryan, Patrick Ryan, Robert M. Ryan, Roy Ryan, W.B. Ryan, William Ryan, Robert Rydeout, Claude Rye, Jesse E. Ryerson, Frank Rynkowski, 1923-1960 (Box-folder 67/9)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Sam Saari, Roy Saas, Reginald Sabol, Savino Sabole, C.A. Sadler, Edwin Saether, Frank Sage, Frank C. Sagen, Fredrick Sailer, Hilario Salas, Felipe Salazar, Frank Salazar, Jerry B. Salazar, Maximilano Salazar, Vernon Arnold Salcido, John Salern, James Salerno, Joseph Salle, John Sallows, Joe Salmon, Wilbur Salmon, Glen Salmonsen, Glenn Elmer Salmonsen, Archie Salois, Clarence Salois, Deway Salois, Dolphe Salois, James Salois, Marion Salois, Melvin W. Salois, D.O. Salsbery, L.P. Salsbury, Raymond Salsbury, Sam Salsbury, William Salsbury, Armulfo Salsido, Robert Salter, Eugene Saltzman, Gerondie Salvador, James Joseph Samples, Elmer Orle Sampson, Fredrick Sampson, Lloyd William Sampson (alias Roy Simpson), Jennings Bryan Sams, 1923-1960 (Box-folder 67/10)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Alejandro Sanchez, John B. Sanchez, Nelson Sanchez, Paul Sandavol, Carl H. Sandberg, Amos J. Sandefur, Benjamin F. Sanders, Cliff Sanders, J.B. Sanders, John H. Sanders, Leo Sanders, Robert Sanders, Robert Ray Sanders, Thomas Sands, Thomas A. Sanders, Elizabeth G. Sandford, John Sands, Irving Sangrey, Ernest L. Sanks, John Harmon Sannan, Joe Santellana, Joseph F. Santos, Andrew Sapien, Hiram Sapp, Ovila Sarasin, Charles Sargent, Eddie Sarmento, Loren Sassen (alias Melvin Lingle), Gus Sather, George Satter, Shed P. Satterfield, John Satterly, LeRoy Saunders, William Saunders, Leonard Lee Saurbier, John Sauter, Bert Savage, Frank Savage, Tom Savala, Barney Savilonis, Jermiah William Savoie, Thomas Savora, George Sawallisch, Howard Sawyer (alias Howard Miller), Roland Sawyer, Harold A. Sayer, Richard J. Sayer, Gardie Lenno Saylors, 1923-1960 (Box-folder 67/11)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Edward Schaaf, Peter Schaak, James Schafer, Ross Schaff, George Schaffer, William Schaffer, Adolf Scharf, Charles Scharf, Anton Scharko, William W. Schattenberg, Godfrey D. Schauer, Charles H. Scheerer, William Scheetz, William Scheffelmier, Edward J. Scheid, Douglas Schelin, Floyd Schelin, Albert Schell, Alan Schendel, Franklin Norman Schenk, Leonard Bernard Schennum, Henry Scherich, Gordon Schied, Joe Schied, Norman W. Schill, Patrick Earl Schimmel, Fred Schindler, Fred Schlagel, Louis Schlagel, Emile Schlatter, Andy Schlenz, Charles Schlenz, Arthur James Schlieper, Dorris E. Schlosser, Uel Schlup, Paul J. Schmalz, Claire Schmidt, Gordon Schmidt, John Schmidt, Donald James Schmitcke, Fred Schneider, George Schneider, 1923-1960 (Box-folder 67/12)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Cecil Albert Schoel, Fred Schofield, Newton Scholtz, Aaron Sylvester Schoolcraft, John Schooley, Charles Lee Schoonover, Lee Eberett Schoonover, Ivan Schrader, Donald Schrantz, Mervin David Schreiner, Arthur Schroeder, Charles E. Schroeder, Henry Schubert, Fred Schullo, Alonzo C. Schultz, Charles Robert Schultz, Dehlia E. Schultz, Marvin Schultz, Richard J. Schultz, Sigmund Schmitz, Raymond Schurch, A.P. Schwartz, Clyde Schwartz, Henry Schwartz, Ray Schwartz, Robert D. Schwartz, Peter Schwind, Walter Scales, Leo F. Scalise, Charles Ray Scammahorn, George H. Scarbro, L.W. Scarbrough, Amos Scott Jr., Charles Scott, Charles Gilbert Scott, Clifford Scott, Danzel Scott, Edward V. Scott, George Scott, Harry Scott, James Scott, James Edgar Scott, Raymond Scott, Raymond Jay Scott, Robert William Scott, Ray Howard Scott, Virgil Scott, William Scott, Glenn Sconton, Cecil Soribner, Homer Soribner, Robert Marlin Scroggins, Chandler Scrogin, Hugh C. Scully, Martin Seals, Elvin Searight, Clarence Searle, Paul Sears, Robert Lorenzo Sears, Willard Seaver, Cleon H. Secord, L.G. Secord, Clifford Sederberg, Ed See, Charles Seed, Harvey Seekins, Richard Lee Seeman, Owen E. Seger, Harold W. Seifort, Lee Allen Seifert, Ed Seimers, David Lowell Selke, Carl J. Sellers, Stanley Sellers, Phillip Sellew, Steve Seion, Charles Shelph, Daniel Selvage, Frederick Seminole, Gilbert Semmens, Theodore A. Senecal, Johnny Senera, Hazel Seng, Warren Seng, Melvin Senne, Finley Sensiba, Leon W. Sensiba Jr., Edward Garcia Senteno, Thomas Septin, Ramon S. Servantes, Luther W. Settlemyre, Charles Severinski, Jack Sewell, Lawrence Sewvielo, Roy Sexe, Jess Seymour, Lawrence Clifford Seymour, Wilbert W. Seymour, Fred Shadoan, Henry Shadoan, Richard Shadoan, Richard Shadoan, Edward Frank Shambo, 1923-1960 (Box-folder 67/13)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Sea - Sham, 1923-1960 (Box-folder 67/14)
    - Prisoner description sheets: Charles M. Shand, Emmett Shandy, George Shane, John Shane, Patrick William Shank, Eugene Shankie, Edward Shanks, Garland E. Shannon Jr., William John Shannon, Billy Ray Shapley, Roger Sharette, Charles Bruce Sharp, Earnest M. Sharp, John Sharp, William Sharp, Perley G. Sharpe, Rex Shartzer, Paul R. Shatto, Albert Shaw Jr., George E. Shaw, Henry Sunny Shaw, Wesley Shaw, Herbert Shea, Jack Shea, Joseph Shean, E. Archie Shear, Gordon Sheehan, Emory Sheely, L. Sheftel, Mike Shein, O.G. Shelby, Olaf Shelby (alias Harry McCurdy), Charles Sheldon, John Sheldon, Lester Sheldon, Raymond Sheldon, Roger W. Shell, Floyd H. Shellum, George Shelton, John E. Shelton, John Shelton, John M. Shelton, Ray Shelton, Pat Howell Shepard, Troy J. Shepard, Gerald Shepherd, Louis Shepherd, Paul Shepherd, Robert Shepherd, 1923-1960 (Box-folder 68/1)